<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CREATE UNSW</title>
    <description>CreateUNSW runs and provides workshops for beginners on electronics, programming, soldering, prototyping and 3D modelling. Weekly sales of electronic components on-campus, including Kits. Hackerspaces and makerspaces. Quadcopters. Funding and support for student projects.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 21:50:35 +1100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 21:50:35 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.6.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>STAR WARS - BCRE8</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Inspired by a love of Star Wars and the recent release of the film Star Wars Episode 7: The Force Awakens, CREATE’s CTO of 2016 Daniel Castillo built and designed a 1:1 scale model of BB8 in the lead up to O-week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daniel has planned and CAD modelled his approach to the BB8 robot which ended up being a single axis pendulum drive system with an integrated reaction wheel for on the spot rotation and turning. The BB8 head is animated by an internal polar system of actuators and held on by a series of neodymium magnets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project is controlled over bluetooth by a PS4 controller and most notably features the use of an Arduino MEGA for processing a PID loop based off IMU feedback to ensure the robot remains stable in drive. The structural composition of the robots includes a laser cut plywood frame covered in 3D printed shells which were graciously provided by the BB8 Builder’s Club.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though not yet prepared, BB8 has been designed to fit modular panels such that animated side panels can be added in future. BB8’s uses have extensive applications in social robotics, general exhibitions, stage performance and autonomous navigation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 20:45:31 +1100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/create-starters/starters-bcre8/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/create-starters/starters-bcre8/</guid>
        
        
        <category>create-starters</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Unmanned Ground Vehicle</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;CREATE is in the process of building its own UGV (Unmanned Ground Vehicle). This will be used as a platform for our members to develop and test autonomous robotic systems without needing a degree in Mechatronics Engineering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Affectionately nicknamed “Deborah” or “Debbie”, the UGV feature motors collected from a second-hand electric wheelchair, a custom-designed and welded steel chassis and a 2D LiDAR.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Projects/ugv3.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Debbie” currently have the capability to drive autonomously in short distances via the use of a GPS guidance system, avoid obstacles in both autonomous and controller mode, and carry a load of 70kg maximum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our current aim is to get the robotic vehicle to navigate itself from lower campus at UNSW Kensington (Anzac Parade) all the way up to the top of campus on Botany St. Not an insignificant distance! As part of this challenge, it will need to navigate itself through wheelchair access routes. We also hope to do various modifications on the platform to enter competitions in the near future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Projects/ugv2.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This project is open to participation from anyone.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 19:45:31 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/projects/UGV/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/projects/UGV/</guid>
        
        
        <category>projects</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pedal Power Generator</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;CREATE partnered up with Bike-ology to develop a pedal-power generator. Bike-ology is a free Arc @ UNSW service where students come together to learn skills on bike repair and maintenance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pedal power generator features an old motor from an electric scooter attached to a used bike frame. A bike chain links the gears of the bike frame and motor together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When pedalling, the magnets inside the motor will spin and low voltage AC (alternating current) electricity is produced at the output. This AC electricity is fed through a full bridge rectifier, which is an electrical circuit that converts AC to DC (direct current) electricity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Projects/bikeology1.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experiment has shown the motor-turned-generator can produce maximum 50V DC when pedalled at Tour de France cyclist speed!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This 50V DC voltage is stepped down to 12V using a DC-DC Buck converter. 12V was chosen as we use car cigarette sockets for the appliances to plug in. We made it such that anything that you can put into the cigarette plug of your car - whether it’d be a phone charging cable or drinks cooler - you can do the same with the pedal power generator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two capacitors were put in parallel with the 12V output from the DC-DC Buck converter. This is to ensure the generator circuit do not ‘switch’ on and off too fast as doing that may cause damage to the electronic devices plugged into the generator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An UNO R3 microcontroller and current sensor was used to control the LED strip which adorns the bike frame. The current sensor detects the amount of current flowing in the whole circuit, and current flow is proportional to the speed at which you’re pedalling. If the value being read from the current sensor is high, the lights on the LED strip will transition from blue to red.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The power output of the pedal power generator is estimated to be around 100W. The bike is able to charge phones, power the aforementioned LED lights, and run a small drinks cooler. It has been featured in several internal UNSW events such as Stress Less Week, and First Friday: Bespoke City at UNSW Art &amp;amp; Design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/CreateUnsw/videos/483971138445013/?permPage=1&quot;&gt;You can view the progress video here.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Projects/bikeology3.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 19:45:31 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/projects/pedal-power-generator/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/projects/pedal-power-generator/</guid>
        
        
        <category>projects</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Vivid Sydney 2016 - Mondrian Cube</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Mondrian Cube was first commissioned for the Vivid Sydney 2016 festival. Taking inspiration from Dutch artist Piet Mondrian and the De Stilj movement, this two-metre-tall interactive lighting installation features bold dark lines enclosing blocks of primary colours. Visitors of the Vivid festival can change the colour arrangement of each side by simply pressing against each rectangular block, thus creating their own Mondrian artwork.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The installation was wholly built and designed by undergraduate UNSW students from different faculties and disciplines. Though the Mondrian Cube, CREATE encouraged members to push beyond their boundaries and manage a real-life engineering project, allowing them to develop valuable skills through student collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(For Behind the Scenes photos &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/CreateUnsw/photos/?tab=album&amp;amp;album_id=590946197747506&quot;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;. To read UNSW Newsroom’s article on the installation, &lt;a href=&quot;http://newsroom.unsw.edu.au/news/students/student-group-create-lights-vivid-mondrian-cube&quot;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Artists:&lt;/b&gt; Christopher Ho, Yunzhen Zhang, Scott Fraser&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Collaborators:&lt;/b&gt; Jessica Tanzil, Laura González Llamazares, Daniel Castillo&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The CREATE Vivid team would like to thank the staff of UNSW Art and Design toolroom (Jim Ward, Alex Byrne, Kamilia Sheppard and Francois Breuillaud-Limondin), for their continual mentorship and support thoughout the construction process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The CREATE Vivid team would also like to thank the following volunteers who have came onboard to help in the assembly and/or final logistical stages of the project:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Laura Lau, Samson Banzi, Nathan Adler, Sam Cassisi, Kate Apel, William Luo, Ray Zeng, Sussane Shaller, Gregory Quirk, Zac Lew, Chris Blundell, Aidan Hartley, Anthony Feizi-Sobbi, Lakshan Jayakody, Austin Kong, Patrick Huang, Ade Doyin Ogunniyi, Roshen Mathews, Kalina Li, William Hales, Alex Yellachich, Jordan Forsyth&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, CREATE acknowledges the following faculties and organisations who have supported the project in one way or another: UNSW Art and Design, Arc @ UNSW, UNSW Engineering, AGB Events, Events Engineering.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 19:45:31 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/projects/mondrian-cube/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/projects/mondrian-cube/</guid>
        
        
        <category>projects</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Robotic Pacman</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;CREATE has built a giant robotic Pacman game! The project appeared at Vivid Sydney 2015, and also featured at a number of events throughout 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Viewers have the opportunity to play as Pacman in his mission to eat all the pellets littered throughout the maze whilst avoiding ghosts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Projects/pacman2.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
The game consists of a large wooden gameboard with robots navigating within the maze. The player controls a Pacman robot via radio control whilst the ghost robots are all AI controlled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/images/Projects/pacman4.jpeg&quot;&gt;See our facebook page for more images.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.abc.net.au/tv/goodgame/stories/s4303926.htm&quot;&gt;Click here to see the project featured on ABC Good Game.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 19:45:31 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/projects/robotic-pacman/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/projects/robotic-pacman/</guid>
        
        
        <category>projects</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UAV Outback Challenge</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;CREATE has been expanding into new territory, one part of which is the formation of a team which is currently working to enter the &lt;a href=&quot;http://uavchallenge.org/medical-express/&quot;&gt; UAV Challenge “Medical Express”&lt;/a&gt; in 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The UAV Challenge has been held in Queensland since 2007, and is an open international competition, with a $50,000 prize for the team with the highest points to successfully complete the challenge. The first challenge, “Search and Rescue”, was successfully completed for the first time last year in 2014 after 8 years, and a new competition specification has been released for the competition to resume in 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CREATE plans to use its considerable experience with UAV development as well as the resources that have been made available through partnerships across the university to enter a competitive team in the 2016 competition. The complexity and demanding nature of the challenge will be rewarding for all participants involved, as well as provide the opportunity for research and academic involvement in the cutting-edge developments that are required to complete the challenge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Projects/uav_logo1.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 19:45:31 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/projects/UAV-Outback-Challenge/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/projects/UAV-Outback-Challenge/</guid>
        
        
        <category>projects</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Start3D - 3D Printer</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We are building 1 METER CUBED 3D printer. The printer will feature a huge build volume, high accuracy printing as well as carbon fiber, nylon, polycarbonate, composite and metal filament printing capabilities. This is an exciting project and a great starting point for anyone new to CREATE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are currently in the process of establishing team roles and structure. We meet every Monday evening at the MCIC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in joining the team, head over to &lt;a href=&quot;/#starters&quot;&gt;CREATE Starters&lt;/a&gt; to sign up.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 19:45:31 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/create-starters/start3d/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/create-starters/start3d/</guid>
        
        
        <category>create-starters</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Light Bridge</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Randwick Council Outdoor Sculpture Walk is a night­time light installation exhibition that third year Sculpture students are putting on in conjunction with Randwick Council. The exhibition has a huge environmental focus, as it coincides with the Randwick Eco­Living Fair on September 13th. I am on the management team of this exhibition, and my specific role is environmental officer. It is my role to ensure that all proposals meet the environmental requirements put to us by their local arborist. The exhibition will run over four nights, and will be attended by the mayor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Light Bridge is artwork I am creating for the exhibition. It will consist of a series of 6-12 pairs of infrared sensor activated lights, that will be installed on a bridge in the Randwick Community Centre wetland. As a person moves over the bridge, each light will go on while they are directly in front of it, and then off as they move on to the next one. It will essentially map a person as they move over the bridge. Bridges are spaces of inbetween-ness, when one is neither at the start nor the beginning. My work attempts to create a space from this non-space and make this period of liminality a focus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Projects/lightbridge2.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Light Bridge Sketch&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is an incredible opportunity to have our work exposed to a vastly different audience, numbering between 6000-­8000 people (as attracted in previous years). In order to make the most of this opportunity, I’m planning quite an ambitious work. My intent in applying for funding is to have my work reach its best potential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scarlett’s work can be viewed in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sF6wnBgo5nc&quot;&gt; Randwick City Council’s video here&lt;/a&gt; (0:30 - 0:33)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Projects/lightbridge3.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Light Bridge Sketch&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 19:45:31 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/create-starters/light-bridge/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/create-starters/light-bridge/</guid>
        
        
        <category>create-starters</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Project Recruitment &amp; First Hackerspace Workshop</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Thanks to everyone who came along to our BBQ on Monday! We’ve got an exciting semester planned with our first Hackerspace workshop of the year coming up and many of our project teams are recruiting. This is a fantastic opportunity to learn some great skills and work with a team to produce a project that you might even get to take to Queensland - read on to find out more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Newsletters/wk2-s1-17-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;hackerspace-w3&quot;&gt;HACKERSPACE W3&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;monday-6-8pm-mcic&quot;&gt;MONDAY 6-8PM MCIC&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;electronics---simple-circuitry-on-breadboards&quot;&gt;ELECTRONICS - Simple Circuitry on Breadboards&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CREATE’s workshop presenter will be guiding us through simple circuitry on breadboards. This workshop is suitable for complete beginners. Anyone can come along and learn, or for some practical experience you can purchase the kit for $10 at the workshop or at our sales stall. See below for the full list of workshops for Sem 1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;sales-stall&quot;&gt;SALES STALL&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;week-3-mon-13-march-12-4pm---globe-lawn&quot;&gt;Week 3 Mon 13 March 12-4pm - Globe Lawn&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t forget our sales stall running every Monday! This will be the perfect place to pick up any electronics components you need such as motors, breadboards or wires, ENGG1000 parts or ask questions  about putting it all together. Check out everything we will be selling on our store website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;quadcopter-orders&quot;&gt;Quadcopter Orders&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Passionate about aerial photography and filming? Want to do your own surveying and mapping? We are now accepting orders for quadcopters!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether you want the thrill of flying or want to take stunning landscape pics, you will love our quadcopter kits, containing everything you need to make it fly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;recruiting---uas&quot;&gt;RECRUITING - UAS&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Newsletters/uas.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
CREATE Unmanned Aerial Systems is looking for new members, especially Compsci students, that have experience in ROS, C++ and image recognition. You will gain extensive experience in the Unmanned Autonomous Vehicle industry and have lots of chances to test your own ideas. Email uas@createunsw.com.au if intereted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;calling-designartscofa-students&quot;&gt;Calling design/arts/COFA students&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come to the Monday Hackerspace workshop for a new project discussion. You may have an opportunity to design the walkway in front of the MCIC building.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;want-to-build-your-own-self-driving-car&quot;&gt;Want to build your own self driving car?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CREATE is looking for new people to join one of our 5 established teams, or to make their own teams, to do just that. Whether you want to do this as a learning experience just for fun, or whether you’re taking yourselves seriously enough to try to become one of the two teams that we send up to a competition in Queensland this year, you should totally come along to our getting-started-again meeting this Monday, 6pm in the MCIC. Special shoutout to anyone who wants to get their hands dirty with OpenCV image processing software, as most teams presently lack a dedicated software person.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 20:45:31 +1100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/newsletters/w2-s1-2017/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/newsletters/w2-s1-2017/</guid>
        
        
        <category>newsletters</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Solder a Light Display</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This week we are continuing the Hackerspace workshops with Part 2 of Electronics! Thanks to those who came to Part 1 last week, if you missed it or want to rewatch, you can find the video recording here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;hackerspace-w4&quot;&gt;HACKERSPACE W4&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;monday-20th-march-6-8pm&quot;&gt;MONDAY (20th March) 6-8PM&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;mcic-ground-floor---electronics---solder-a-light-display&quot;&gt;MCIC Ground Floor - ELECTRONICS - Solder a light display&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come down to Michael Crouch Innovation Centre on the ground floor of the Material Science building for Part 2 of the Electronics workshop with CREATE!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week we’re continuing with working on electronics and learning how to solder, and how it is useful in circuit design. If you missed the first part or you’re a complete beginner, you can still buy the kit and follow along while making your own interactive lighting circuit. Kits are $10 and are available at the workshop or on our Monday sales stall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The workshop is FREE along with the PIZZA after, so come along, learn a cool new skill, make some new friends with the same interests all while getting fed for the night! If you can’t make it to the workshop, watch our live stream &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/c/createunsw/live&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; on YouTube. Join us on the Facebook event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Newsletters/wk3-s1-17-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;sales-stall&quot;&gt;SALES STALL&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;w4-mon-20-march-12-4pm---globe-lawn&quot;&gt;W4 Mon 20 March 12-4pm - Globe Lawn&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take your selfies to a whole new level with our quadcopters, now selling on CREATE’s website and sales stall! We’re on every Monday at Globe Lawn and everything we sell is on our online store. If you can’t make it, you can buy online and send us an email to arrange a pickup time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;This photo above of Where’s Wally revellers in Cyprus was one of the winners in the 2015 International Drone Photography Contest. Scroll down for some more stunning aerial pictures you could take. We wish we were still on holidays!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Newsletters/wk3-s1-17-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Newsletters/wk3-s1-17-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;recruiting---uas&quot;&gt;RECRUITING - UAS&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Newsletters/uas.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;CREATE UAS&quot; /&gt;
CREATE Unmanned Aerial Systems is looking for new members, especially Compsci students, that have experience in ROS, C++ and image recognition. You will gain extensive experience in the Unmanned Autonomous Vehicle industry and have lots of chances to test your own ideas. Email uas@createunsw.com.au if intereted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Newsletters/self-driving.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;want-to-build-your-own-self-driving-car&quot;&gt;Want to build your own self driving car?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CREATE is looking for new people to join one of our 5 established teams, or to make their own teams, to do just that. Whether you want to do this as a learning experience just for fun, or whether you’re taking yourselves seriously enough to try to become one of the two teams that we send up to a competition in Queensland this year, you should totally come along to our getting-started-again meeting this Monday, 6pm in the MCIC. Special shoutout to anyone who wants to get their hands dirty with OpenCV image processing software, as most teams presently lack a dedicated software person.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2017 20:45:31 +1100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/newsletters/w3-s1-2017/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/newsletters/w3-s1-2017/</guid>
        
        
        <category>newsletters</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
